Boss Su,
we haven't met for a few days.
Shouldn't you settle
the agreed-upon wages?
You want wages for an unfinished job?
No, I don't.
It hurts.
I don't have any cash on me.
In a couple of days...
I can wait a few days.
But the money for Dabao's candy...
You said
you could hire someone.
Do you want the money?
Let go of me.
Wait here.
You have a bright future.
Do you know the rules of the agency?
No.
Thirty taels of silver
and you'll be hired immediately.
That's enough.
Remember to come to work tomorrow.
Wait.
What's wrong with you?
How dare you lie to me?
I'll take your hand.
Su's Escort Agency
never lies to anyone.
We're family from now on.
How can I lie to you?
Don't worry.
Go.
Come to work tomorrow.
Mr. Su,
remember to call me next time.
Come here.
If you dare to pinch me again,
I'll make you have no candy to eat.
Go, go, go.
Goodbye, Mr. Su.
The brain is a good thing,
but you don't have it.
So when do we move?
If you don't move, you'll live here.
Mr. Su, just let me go.
Even if I can get up at 3 a.m. every day,
I can't do anything
with this noise in the morning.
If your brother comes to fix the broken board again,
I'm afraid the Xingyun Conference...
I've found you a room in Huayue Tower.
You can go there at 5 a.m. every day
to read and sleep.
as you wish.
So living in the agency is to shut people up.
In Huayue Tower, you can prepare for the Starry Night Gala.
Great.
Then,
you'll pay the rent, right?
I will.
You're so thoughtful.
Cheng Qi, thank you.
New bedding.
There are beds available,
Why do you have to make yourself suffer?
Don't catch a cold and get sick.
Otherwise, everyone will suffer with you.
Thank you, my lady.
The furnishings in this room
were all specially arranged by Ms. Tang.
You are truly blessed.
I'm afraid you've got it wrong.
My wife is just understanding.
Ms. Tang
is a person of righteousness.
Thank you.
Mr. Su is really good to you.
She left you breakfast in the morning,
and gave you an extra quilt at night.
She also arranged such a nice room for you.
I
wanted to test her,
but she really agreed.
Miss Su
is really a tough but tender person.
My Lord,
it's good to stay
in the Escort Agency.
Yeah, it's good.
But we've been through a lot.
Don't forget
what we're here for.
Cheng Qi,
you must
win the championship in the Starry Sky Conference.
My Lord,
I want to go out.
To the Moon God Pavilion?
Be quick.
Are you two playing?
Focus.
I've told you,
your money only gets you in.
You can't choose who to work for.
If she doesn't want you,
no refund.
Let's go.
Jiaojiao,
this new escort
will be with you from now on.
New escort?
I don't want him.
You can keep him.
Good intentions taken for granted.
He's a really good prospect.
If he's not good enough, he can follow me.
Name?
Age?
Where are you from?
What are you good at?
Bai Yanliang.
21.
I live in the east of the capital.
I'm good at using a broadsword.
The east?
I live in Ning'an.
I'm frank
and simple-minded.
Gong Xi.
- My Lord. - It hurts.
Please.
You were holding back.
Go get the escort uniform.
My Lord,
no new design,
but I found an old one.
Make do with it for now.
Later, I'll have Gong Xi
to make you a new one.
No need.
This is fine.
Su Yuejiao,
my life
is yours from now on.
Just a escort,
not a lifelong contract.
Just protect the goods.
Well,
I'll call you Bai from now on.
You're the same as Gong Xifacaicheng.
Call me boss.
Oh, no.
I knew she would run away.
I always open the door at 9 a.m.
Remember next time.
I thought about it all night.
Even if you're not with Miss Yan,
the Moon God Pavilion is still a scam.
How much do you make
following your master?
No money.
I and my master
have no money.
How dare you say this is a black shop?
If you work for me in the future,
I'll give you one taels of silver
for an hour.
How about it?
Boss,
what do you need me to do?
What did Meng Feifei do to you?
My Lord,
will you be here all day from now on?
What?
Are you going to work here tomorrow?
Yes.
Young man,
don't play with fire.
You may be tired out.
Won't he be tired working like this?
He just came here for the first time,
and he's recommended by my uncle.
There must be something wrong.
What's wrong with working?
He works so hard,
which makes us look lazy.
Then he can replace us and escort with My Lord.
Split from inside.
Uncle replaces My Lord.
Kill two birds with one stone.
We must not let him succeed.
I'm back.
Let me tell you.
thanks for your help.
I've been working hard these days,
and I've got a lot of ideas.
That's great.
Or you'd blame me for your writer's block.
You're so smart-mouthed.
No, I'm not.
I'll pay back the rent
after the Star Conference.
It's already deducted from your salary.
You... you're exploiting me.
I...
Don't you dare touch her!
I'm her husband.
Who are you?
What did you say?
I said I'm Su Yuejiao's husband.
My dear, my honey.
With your face?
I don't approve!
Bro,
it doesn't matter if you approve or not.
Is he good at fighting?
I fell in love with her at first sight.
We love each other.
We are predestined.
We are soulmates.
Never mind.
Who are you?
I'm
the new escort.
The new escort?
If you are the new escort,
you should learn from Gong Xi and Facha
how to escort.
My lady,
let's go.
Bro,
you don't have to work so hard.
If you are so willing to work,
I'll leave the hitching to you tomorrow.
I'm also a servant.
My Lord,
we robbed the escort
of the Fuyun Escort Agency.
Good job.
How's the investigation going?
After we robbed Su, he went to Ning'an County.
He got married a few days after he came back.
Wait for my message.
Ask all the brothers to come here.
The food here
is good.
I see.
My Lord
You are an undercover
and want to infiltrate the enemy.
Brilliant!
If you want to eat freshly fried dough sticks tomorrow,
go out early and eat them yourself.
I have to escort in the morning.
I don't have time to buy for you.
Okay, my wife.
There's no one else here.
Who are you acting for?
Here.
Love each other.
My dear wife.
Bao and the Seven Fairies.
Did you write all these?
No.
Then why do you give them to me?
I don't like reading.
The point is not reading.
We agreed to pretend to be a couple.
We should look like a real couple.
We can't be obviously fake.
Right?
And
Bai Yanli
is targeting me from the beginning.
I seriously suspect that
your uncle is testing us.
He can't do that.
You are not sensible enough.
You should learn from these books
from these books.
I think you are right.
But I can fight,
but I get sleepy
when I read.
I've thought about it.
These books
are full of pictures.
You'll understand at a glance.
You won't get sleepy.
Take care, my wife.
Give it to me.
My dear,
you've worked hard.
Today,
you should also do your best.
You're shameless
and brazen.
Come back early.
I'll wait for you
to have dinner.
Is your master always like this?
Basically.
But our master never does this.
Why don't you work?
Have you ever thought that
if I move,
I can't get out of this door at noon.
The rules of the Escort Agency.
If you are lazy,
you have to leave.
The escort agency's rules are for the escorts to follow.
They are not escorts.
You have principles.
I appreciate that.
If there are new escorts, you can manage them.
Yicheng,
let me test you.
Do you recognize all these characters?
Star Cloud retest,
gather all the elegance,
need to use the clear smoke cloud rabbit
to write down the extraordinary.
Please prepare it.
Sir,
what does it mean?
The inkstone, ink, paper, and brush
are the best in the Yun State.
How can we afford them?
I have money.
You have private money?
No.
I earned it.
Yicheng,
just keep your hard-earned money.
Besides,
it's not enough.
The rice paper from the Cloud Bookshop
is indeed of the highest quality.
Thank you, my lady.
There's no one else around,
so stop calling me that.
It's quite cheesy.
I didn't realize attending the Starry Night
to attend the Starry Sky Festival.
Red clay inkstone,
pine soot ink,
cloud-patterned paper, and rabbit hair brush.
These are essentials for a refined scholar.
It's not too much to ask.
If the writing isn't good,
the tools are useless.
But I remember you told me
you don't like studying.
Yeah.
I feel sleepy as soon as I open a book.
You're right.
Most of the poets nowadays
are just pretentious.
Why do you want to compete with them?
If I can win the contest
and gain popularity,
I can change this trend.
My book
must make you want to read it,
and the common people of the Yun State.
Reading is a good thing.
And good books are nourishing,
they can nurture the people,
allowing goodness to take root,
and help our Yun State
achieve peace and prosperity.
But these papers
have already cost me all my monthly salary.
You've helped me a lot already.
I'll figure out the rest myself.
What can you do now?
How about this?
I'll lend you the money.
Chengni inkstone,
from Jiangzhou.
A rabbit-hair brush,
from here.
A pine soot ink,
from Xuanzhou.
A Jiangzhou...
They're all here.
How do you get so many treasures?
Every time I escort to a new place,
I'll buy some local specialties.
When these boxes are all filled,
I'll have traveled all over the Yun State.
Amazing!
But with so many treasures,
be careful they get stolen.
This is my secret collection.
No one knows.
My brother just made
this box for me.
Then I'm the first
to know your secret.
Yeah.
So if anything gets stolen,
it must be you.
You're so nice to me.
I want the seal,
and you want the top.
You helped me,
I must help you.
Why is Ning'an empty?
Where's the book I gave you?
How dare you say that?
I remember
the specialty is Zhuangyuan cake.
But you insisted it was your book.
I can't put food here.
I'll treat you later.
Put the book back.
Or I'll throw it away.
You...
Those things are useful.
Return them after use.
My dear,
I added honey to the soy milk.
Try it while it's hot.
I don't like sweet.
Then
try this fried dough stick.
I bought it for you at the morning market.
My Lord,
it's almost time.
Let's go.
My Lady,
I'll go to Huayue Tower first.
You escort the goods today.
Don't be too tired.
Okay.
I've never seen him get up so early.
He said he was going to see Tang Xin first.
You...
Yicheng!
Wait!
Help me up.
Your face is swollen.
My sister treats you with sincerity.
You go to the tavern every day, fine.
But you also want to take advantage of Tang Xin.
Do you think we are easy to bully?
Stop!
I'll deal with you two later.
Are you alright?
It's nothing serious.
Just a scratch.
What are you waiting for?
The Starry Night is about to start.
Faca, get the carriage ready.
I'll take you to Huayue Tower.
Let's go.
Next up,
the one about to take the stage
took a unique approach in the preliminary round,
in the first round,
and won
the love of many people.
So this time,
what question did he draw?
Can he stand out again?
Let's wait and see.
My lady, you don't have to.
You didn't dodge when you saw the knife.
Are you crazy?
When he swung the knife,
I suddenly remembered
how to answer the question,
so I didn't have time to dodge.
This is just right.
Just right for the performance.
You've been studying too hard.
And you,
eat so much every day,
but you can't even pull your master away.
Next, let's welcome Cheng Qi.
Mr. Cheng.
What time is it?
What's going on?
Cheng Qi withdrew from the competition.
Miss,
I haven't heard of anyone withdrawing.
I saw Mr. Cheng debating with others yesterday.
Let's welcome Mr. Cheng.
Come on.
Why is he so late?
Looking around the Lishan Mountain,
the Epang Palace was burnt down.
The dust of the Qin Dynasty has turned into smoke.
No red candle and curtain,
no laughter of children.
The Zhou, Qi,
the Qin, the Han, and the Chu.
A broken stele in rain, a lone tomb at dusk.
The hegemony has turned into dust.
Kings and dukes returned to grass after a thousand years.
The fame and wealth have been given to the wild goose.
If I had known,
to care about winning or losing?
Winning
is just temporary.
Losing
Everything is empty.
What is attachment?
Good, good.
Wonderful.
How's that?
Didn't I bring glory to you?
It's worth using my treasure to help you.
I heard
Ling Feng
passed the second test.
Yes.
He recited the poem my father asked.
But there's a young man
who seems to be more popular than him.
You let him go straight to the final test.
What's his name?
Cheng Qi,
son of the magistrate of Ning'an County.
Ning'an County?
Son of Cheng Zheng?
I think
Cheng Qi
is the top choice.
If he becomes
the top scholar,
he'll be a money-making tool,
completely detached from the court's
and can be discarded at any time.
How is
his writing?
It's bold
and delicate.
He's indeed rare.
But if he takes after his father,
he'll be hard to control in the future.
Check his writings
carefully.
If anything inappropriate
to the emperor.
I see.
I will keep an eye on him.
I didn't expect you to write
such a bold poem.
My Lady,
these two things
are not related at all.
Fortunately, the wound is not deep.
It should be healed
after two more changes of medicine.
I didn't expect
you always wear armor,
but you still buy makeup.
I just buy some specialties.
It's the same as yours.
I know you don't want to
throw away my books.
You don't need it anyway.
Give it back to me.
You can't take back what you gave.
It's a unique book.
the only one in the Yun State.
I can't give it back to you.
When you become the champion,
it will be priceless.
It can be
the reward for borrowing these things.
Why do you think I can win?
Who else can it be but you?
I watched you from the audience.
You are outstanding.
Since you said so,
then the top scholar must be me.
When we return to Ning'an,
I'll treat you to Zhuangyuan pastries.
You said that?
Deal.
Because of Cheng Qi,
my brother and Bai Yanli were banned from escorting.
I'm exhausted.
Xin,
what are those girls downstairs
What are they doing
downstairs?
You don't know?
Those girls downstairs
are all waiting to see
Cheng Qi's charm.
By the way,
if they know you are Cheng Qi's wife,
the escort agency will be lively.
Why?
When can I come out?
Mr. Cheng's battle makeup is so handsome.
It makes me feel like
a general fighting bravely on the battlefield.
I never thought he could write lyrics like this.
From now on,
Mr. Cheng is my true destiny.
Why hasn't he come out yet?
He wasn't caught by some lady
and made a guest, was he?
Don't slander Mr. Cheng.
He's not that kind of person.
How can those girls accept
that their beloved gentleman has a wife?
That's not the worst.
If they know
he's a live-in son-in-law,
you'll become the target of all.
Those girls will probably eat you alive.
But what if they know
you're fake?
They'll tear down the agency.
I dare them.
You have no idea
how crazy those women are for Cheng Qi.
Come on, Cheng Qi's portrait.
Two taels each.
Limited to 100 copies.
First come, first served.
Sorry, sold out.
Since you all like Mr. Cheng so much,
I'll
I'll try to get more for you.
Besides,
we're gonna launch a new service.
What's that?
What do you mean?
Want to know if you're
a match for Mr. Cheng?
Yes!
Want to know his pick for a wife?
Be back tomorrow
at this time.
Great!
Awesome!